good afternoon everyone
so now it's finally time for our next
question
uh so it's the fourth question of the
day
uh i hope that most of you had
participated in the last question as
well
and i wish that uh all of you will be
participating in the next questions also
so this is the question on the screen so
this is the total ninth question uh
in in our all 75 questions
and it is the fourth question of the day
so let's see what the
question is you are waiting
in a signal for a long time in a big
queue
on your left is a pavement you will
and your options are a wait till signal
turn screen
b drive on the pavement see
honk continuously d argue with
pedestrians
so uh this is the question
uh and you know we are having these
questions
uh every day every day we are having
five
questions and we uh by simply
by simply answering these questions
you can win these prizes uh you know
this quiz
competition uh you can choose
either if you want a bike safety kit or
a car safety kit
so uh you know with this
a little thing with just answering a
small
question you can win this prize and
also that we should also learn from this
uh i am repeating this question once
again
you are waiting in a signal for a long
time in a big queue
on your left is a payment you will
uh so i'll just repeat the question once
again in hindi also
signals
[Music]
in giving you all these questions they
are
of making sure that everyone is aware
and all of us are following these uh
road safety rules uh and
you know like we have this small
[Music]
whoever gives the correct answer will be
winning these
prizes uh so it is really
great that uh with
a little step with by just doing a small
thing
and that is to just answer this
question regarding road safety
uh we can save lives you know uh all of
us are road users we all either drive or
as a pedestrian
uh wherever we have to go we will have
to use the road
uh you know it is just not possible that
one uh does not use the roads and that
is why
we must know that uh they should be safe
you know
all of us use roads but still
it is not the safest means of transport
we but we will have to make it the
safest means of transport
we will have to make sure that not more
many people die because of this
you know millions of us drive on these
indian roads
every day and 400 people they die
because of road crashes happening every
day
and then just by answering this small
question
just by knowing the results uh you know
you will
you will at least learn something from
this and then
you will know that what i can do in
such situations we will learn a lot
uh by just answering uh this
small question and the biggest thing is
that
we will save many lives also
so uh i'm just repeating the question
again
uh you are waiting in a signal for a
long time
in a big queue on your left is a
pavement
you will a wait till signal turns green
b drive on the pavement see
how continuously they argue with the
pedestrians
so yes
[Music]
uh this question it will be there for
the next two hours from now
and you can simply answer this question
uh and ask others also ask your friends
and family also
to try to answer this and the results
uh and the results they will be
announced
uh every day at 10 pm we have a show
called bluntly speaking
the results will be announced in that
and also you can see the list of the
winners
uh the the results you can also see on
our website
uh you can go there also and check the
names
as well as uh in the show we will get
our results as well as the answers also
in case you have uh uh
um
as i said earlier also millions of us
uh i'll say that all of us we all drive
on
indian roads uh you know we are actually
using these roads
either as uh either as a driver
or either as a pedestrian somehow we are
using the roads every day but there is a
problem and that is
it is not the safest means of transport
you know
415 people they drive
every day they die every day on these
roads just because they are not
following
these traffic rules and they do not have
the awareness
that what they should be doing so
uh so to avoid that our first step
it will be to create awareness
and uh this quiz it's a medium of giving
everyone such awareness that why
it is important why is it
necessary to make sure that everyone is
safe
you know let's just let's just uh take
a a small example which people
uh do not follow and that is over
speeding let's take over speeding so
what happens
uh when a person is over speeding
they are not only putting their lives at
a risk
they are putting others lives also at a
risk
which is really dangerous and people do
not understand that
why it is important why is it necessary
to know that
we must follow all these road safety
rules because they are for our
own safety and to promote uh
and hence to promote this message
of uh of road safety that we should be
uh driving on indian roads safely or if
we are a pedestrian
then we should know the basic awareness
that
how our behavior should be there
on the roads so i'm repeating the
question
again so it is you are waiting
in a signal for a long time in a big
queue on your left is a pavement
you will a wait till
signal turns green drive on the pavement
see home continuously be
argue with the pedestrians uh so
uh you may well hindi maybe repeat
[Music]
it is really simple to answer i'm
repeating once again
uh so it is really easy to answer this
question what you simply have to do
is there uh there will be a link in the
description box
either you can answer this question uh
with
that link or you can answer this on our
youtube page or
on our facebook page and just by doing
this simple step
and just by doing this simple step
just by simply answering this
small question you can save many
lives you can uh you can
get awareness yourself you will learn a
lot by answering these questions
simply uh you know you will create
awareness
uh
you know this question will be valid for
next
you will get awareness you will create
awareness
and you will save millions of
lives of those people who are dying
on indian roads every day and the
biggest thing is that you can get
get these prizes also either you will
get a bike safety kit
for you and your family or you will get
a car
safety kit so just
by doing this simple step
you know it's like an act of kindness of
telling people
that why road safety is very important
all our questions they are related to
road safety only they are related to
different topics of road safety some are
related to helmets some are related to
pedestrian awareness
so these uh questions uh they are
related to this and just by simply
answering them
uh you you can save many lives
so the results of this we have
every day we have a show at 10 pm called
bluntly speaking
either you will get the results there
uh you will get the results as well as
the answers
every day there and also you can check
those on
the results on our website also
so i'm repeating this question one more
time
uh you are waiting in a signal for a
long
time in a big queue uh
on your left is a pavement you will
a wait till signal turns green
b drive on the pavement see
honk continuously d argue with the
pedestrians
so i hope
this was the fourth question of today so
the next question
uh i will request all
so that's it for right now uh you will
be soon getting your next question
also in uh in two hours so
thank you so much everyone